# **Madeleine Harris**

Atlanta, GA, 30309 | mmlh.harris@gmail.com

**Github:** <a href="https://github.com/miss-mad/">https://github.com/miss-mad/</a> | **Portfolio:** <a href="https://miss-mad.github.io/portfolio/">https://miss-mad.github.io/portfolio/</a> | **LinkedIn:** <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/madeleine-m-harris/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/madeleine-m-harris/</a>

### **SUMMARY**

Self-motivated full stack web developer with a unique and varied background in healthcare, retail, event coordination, property management, accounting, and the fine arts. This wide array of experience culminates in a meticulous, disciplined, and ever-inquisitive fast learner. Excited to bring new technical and development skills, combined with existing knowledge and skill, to this flourishing field of web development.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Languages:** Git, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6 and CommonJS), SQL, NoSQL, GraphQL **Frameworks:** CSS Frameworks (Materialize CSS, Bootstrap CSS), Express, MySQL **Libraries:** jQuery, Sequelize, MongoDB and Mongoose, Apollo, React, Ant Design **Core Concepts:** Mobile-First Design, Local and Session Storage, APIs, Object-Oriented Programming, User Authentication, Agile Methodology, Github and Heroku Deployment

# **PROJECTS**

#### ResuMade

https://github.com/miss-mad/ResuMade | https://resumade.herokuapp.com/

- Easily create professional resumes here
- Role: React form + ant design
- Tools: React, Stripe, JavaScript, Express, Apollo, GraphQL, MongoDB, jsonwebtoken

# Who's App

https://github.com/miss-mad/whos-app | https://whooos-app.herokuapp.com/

- The newest anonymous and secure messaging app is here! Who is it you'll be talking to?
- Role: Project manager + Socket.io
- Tools: Socket.io, JavaScript, Node, Express, Sequelize, MySQL, Handlebars, Bootstrap

#### **MTHSY Music**

https://github.com/miss-mad/mthsy-music | https://miss-mad.github.io/mthsy-music/

- A one-stop shop for music information and upcoming events for music artists
- Role: lastFM API + local storage
- Tools: JavaScript, HTML, Materialize CSS, APIs: lastFM, YouTube, TicketMaster

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Pharmacy Technician**

2021 - Present

Walgreens Marietta, GA

Highly communicative to 100s of patients of all ages to ensure timely medication requests' fulfillment while efficiently taking in new prescriptions, filling existing orders, and checking out waiting patients. Meticulously sorted the day's incoming medicine order to ensure out of stock items are completed while also coordinating various vaccine appointments and COVID testing.

**CME Coordinator** 2019 – 2020

American Medical Forum

Alpharetta, GA

Built 15 new events into the company website via Wordpress and WooCommerce. Repeatedly coordinated periodic nationwide medical conferences with 100s of healthcare professional attendees. Facilitated participant experience from registration to the CME credit claiming process by email, phone, and chat.

# **Licensed Property Manager**

2018 - 2019

HomeOwners Advantage

Atlanta, GA

Project manager for the \$143,691 gym renovation June – September 2018. Attended and minuted bi-monthly evening Board and Finance Committee meetings. Oversaw the master association and the 7-member concierge team while routinely surveilling the property, organizing necessary maintenance and repairs.

# **EDUCATION**

**Certificate in Full Stack Web Development:** Georgia Institute of Technology, Atlanta, GA, 2022 **Bachelor of Arts:** Cum Laude with Honors, Kennesaw State University, Kennesaw, GA